<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AMindfullQuit</string>

    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="cigarette_data">Cigarette Data</string>
    <string name="meditation_data">Meditation data</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="empty_meditation_graph">Complete your first meditation to see your progress</string>
    <string name="empty_smoking_graph">Go to settings to start logging your progress</string>
    <string name="presentation">Presentation</string>
    <string name="hi_there">Hi there !</string>
    <string name="mail">mail@mail.com</string>

    <string-array name="currency_array">
        <item>€</item>
        <item>$</item>
        <item>£</item>
        <item>*</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- R E F E R E N C E S -->
    <string name="reference_one">
        Brewer, Judson A., et al. \"Mindfulness training for smoking cessation: results from a
        randomized controlled trial.\" Drug and alcohol dependence 119.1-2 (2011): 72-80.
    </string>

    <!-- D E V E L O P E R -->
    <string name="presentation_developer">
        My name is Lucas, I stumbled across an article, during my master’s degree in Cognitive Sciences,
        showing great results for smoking cessation using simple meditation techniques. In fact,
        subjects showed greater success (31%) than using traditional smoking cessation programs (6%),
        with fewer relapses and improved well-being !
    </string>
    <string name="pass_knwoledge_developer">
        I then decided to pass on this knowledge, developing this mobile app on my free time.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_developer">
        For any suggestions or to report bugs you can contact me via mail:
    </string>
    <string name="donation_developer">
        I decided to let this app 100% free and without ads. If you’d like to support,
        please consider making a small donation via GooglePlay.
    </string>
    <string name="buy_coffee">Buy me a coffee</string>
    <string name="buy_sandwich">Buy me a sandwich</string>


    <!-- P R I N C I P L E S -->
    <string name="mindful_smoking">MindFul Smoking</string>
    <string name="rain">R.A.I.N.</string>
    <string name="sitting_meditation">Sitting Meditation</string>
    <string name="every_day_activities">Everyday Activities</string>

    <string name="welcome">
        <big><u>Welcome</u></big> <i>to</i><br />
        <b>Android</b>!
    </string>

    <!-- D E S C  I P T I O N S -->
    <string name="mindful_smoking_description">
        Developing awareness of your smoking habits and breaking noxious automatisms
    </string>

    <string name="rain_description">
        Recognize - Accept - Investigate - Note
    </string>

    <string name="sitting_meditation_description">
        Reinforcing your mental strength
    </string>

    <string name="daily_activities_description">
        Develop a long term habit of being mindful by incorporating it in your everyday life
    </string>

    <!-- P R I N C I P L E S -->
    <string name="mindful_instructions">
        <![CDATA[
        <i>This step is to consider only if you haven\'t completely stopped your cigarette consumption yet.</i>
        <br/>
        Along the years and thousands of cigarettes smoked in our life, the act of smoking has become
        an habit.
        An habit is a behaviour we tend to perform without any conscious effort, simply responding to
        automatisms we have developed carrying out an action for a numerous amount of repetitions.
        The goal of this exercise is to break up this pattern. For that, we only have to bring back to
        our attention the act of smoking in itself, so that it becomes again an active behaviour on which we
        have control rather something we execute in the back of our mind.
       <br/>
       <br/>
       Here\'s an example of a "mindful smoke" to illustrate the concept, of course you don\'t have to
       follow everything to the word, adapt your practice given your own perception.
       <br/> <i>
       While I grab a cigarette out of my pack, I take a close look at it, inspecting wrinkles in the
       paper, there is a slight bend in the form. As I light it up, the flame heats my skin. I can
       hear the tobacco crackling and feel the bitter taste of smoke running through my mouth. I
       imagine the smoke spreading in my lungs, as I exhale, I feel the air hitting my palate, etc…
        </i><br/>
        <br/>
        Your mind will wonder while you practice, don\'t worry it is perfectly normal. Once you\'ve realized
        that you got lost in your train of thoughts just gently come back to mindfulness.
        <br/>
        <br/>
        After a few days of this exercise, or even a few attempts, you might realize that you avoided
        a couple of cigarettes during the day, the ones you used to light up without even noticing.
        Very often, people realize how bad a cigarette tastes if you\'re paying attention, enough to
        bring the question \"Why am I smoking by the way ?\".
        <b>smoking</b>
        !]]></string>

    <string name="rain_instructions">
        <![CDATA[
        A method based on scientific researches which has
        been proven highly efficient in several studies.
        <i>Refining our perception of cravings</i><br/>
        <big><b><u>Recognize</u></b></big>
        Firstly, we have to train our ability to recognize when cravings occurs. It may sometimes be
        obvious: while you see someone lighting a cigarette in front of you, you suddenly feel the
        urge to do the same. But it can also be a subtle sensation, maybe feeling a bit grumpy waking
        up this morning.<br/>
        Either way, we want to bring this feeling to our awareness rather than letting it silently affect us.
        The goal here isn\'t trying to shut it down, thought you might be able to do so for a certain period
        of time, it will eventually resurface ten times stronger. We do not resist the wave, we surf on it.
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <big><b><u>Accept<u><b/></big>
        Needless to say, easier said than done.

        <i>Refining our perception of cravings</i><br/>
        <big><b><u>Recognize</u></b></big>
        Firstly, we have to train our ability to recognize when cravings occurs. It may sometimes be
        obvious: while you see someone lighting a cigarette in front of you, you suddenly feel the
        urge to do the same. But it can also be a subtle sensation, maybe feeling a bit grumpy waking
        up this morning.<br/>
        Either way, we want to bring this feeling to our awareness rather than letting it silently affect us.
        The goal here isn\'t trying to shut it down, thought you might be able to do so for a certain period
        of time, it will eventually resurface ten times stronger. We do not resist the wave, we surf on it.
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <big><b><u>Accept<u><b/></big>
        Needless to say, easier said than done.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="sitting_instructions">
        <![CDATA[
        <big><u>Welcome</u></big> <i>to</i><br />
        <b>sitting</b>!
        The benefits of a daily meditation practice are well documented
        by science, including cognition abilities, emotional control and health improvement
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="everyday_instructions">
        <![CDATA[
        <big><u>Welcome</u></big> <i>to</i><br />
        <b>everyday</b>!
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="donation">Donation</string>
    <string name="helping_hand">Helping hand</string>
    <string name="buy_me_a_coffee">Buy me a coffee</string>
    <string name="buy_me_a_sandwich">Buy me a sandwich</string>


</resources>
